<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notes on Octemull&#39;s Personal Site</title>
    <link>https://octemull.github.io/personal-site/tags/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notes on Octemull&#39;s Personal Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 11:52:59 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://octemull.github.io/personal-site/tags/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Singles Day can tell us about how retail is changing in China</title>
      <link>https://octemull.github.io/personal-site/post/w3-china_singles_day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 11:52:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://octemull.github.io/personal-site/post/w3-china_singles_day/</guid>
      <description>Paper  Title: What Singles Day can tell us about how retail is changing in China Authors: Lambert Bu, Anne Kronschnabl, Kelly Ungerman, Daniel Zipser Year: 2018 Link: What Singles Day can tell us about how retail is changing in China Tags: Open Access: Yes  Notes Why  Singles Day is the largest single-day sales even over the world, and its influence is becoming wider. Biggest sales  $45 billion purchased made in 24-hour period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequences of purchases in credit card data reveal lifestyles in urban populations</title>
      <link>https://octemull.github.io/personal-site/post/w3-sequence-purchase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 10:51:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://octemull.github.io/personal-site/post/w3-sequence-purchase/</guid>
      <description>Paper  Title: Sequences of purchases in credit card data reveal lifestyles in urban populations Authors: Riccardo Di Clemente, Miguel Luengo-Oroz, Matias Travizano, Sharon Xu, Bapu Vaitla &amp;amp; Marta C. González DOI: 10.1038/s41467-018-05690-8 Tags: Year: 2018 Open Access: Yes  Notes What  A framework was defined using a text compression technique on the sequences of credit card purchases to cluster different patterns of collective behaviors. Five consumer groups which shared similar characteristics were found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detecting influenza epidemics using search engine query data</title>
      <link>https://octemull.github.io/personal-site/post/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 11:37:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://octemull.github.io/personal-site/post/hugo/</guid>
      <description>Paper  Title: Detecting influenza epidemics using search engine query data Authors: Jeremy Ginsberg, Matthew H. Mohebbi, Rajan S. Patel, Lynnette Brammer, Mark S. Smolinski &amp;amp; Larry Brilliant DOI: 10.1038/nature07634 Tags: Year: 2009  Summary  What
 Propose a method of analyzing large numbers of Google search queries to track influenza-like illness in a population which can shorten reporting lag for 1-2 weeks.  Why analyze Google queries possible</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>